CS-700 Assignment 3

This assignment contains a program to create a banking system application which adds account, deposit money, withdraw money and display account details.

1. Main file containing both modules.
	a. Summary - . Running the main() function will the bank system module.
	b. It contains the following file :
		i. main.cpp

2. Banking application -
	a. Summary - Running this program will allow you to add accounts, make deposit, withdraw money, get interest and check all the transactions with your details.
	b. It contains the following files :
		i. customer.cpp - stores customer details
		ii. customer.h - contains functions for customer
		iii. Date.cpp - Date file
		iv. Date.h - stores date functions
		v. transaction.cpp - stores all the transaction details
		vi. transaction.h - contains transaction functions
		vii. account.cpp - stores all the account details
		viii. account.h - contains functions for account
		ix. BankApplication.cpp - runs the bank application
		x. BankApplication.h - contains function to run bank application
		xi. bank.cpp - performs operations to add, deposit, withdraw and check account.
		xii. bank.h - contains functions for all bank related Operations.

Github Repo Link -> https://github.com/syedfaisaljaved/cs700-Assignment3
